Guide to the Bryant Fleming plans, [ca. 1904-1937]
Fleming, Bryant plans
- Series I. Clients A-H
  - Dunlap, Esq., D. A. Location: Toronto, Ontario
    - Perspective sketch in garden, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 342
    - Plan of drives, walk, drainage and electric conduits to gates, Undated (Folder 20)
      Sheet # 343
    - Rough sketch of site plan, Undated (Folder 20)
      Sheet # 344
  - English High School Location: Waterbury, Connecticut
    - Plans of floor, 1918 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1367
    - Plans of floor, 1918 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1368
  - Fillmore Avenue Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Proposed improvement, 1906 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1502
    - Proposed improvement, 1906 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1503
    - Proposed improvement, Undated (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1504
  - Fisher, W. A. Location: Detroit, Michigan
    - Sketch study of Balustrade on Arrival Court, 1926 (Folder 10)
      Sheet # 104
    - Sketch study of Beacon Light entrance, Undated (Folder 10)
      Sheet # 105
  - Fort Rensselaer Club Location: Canajoharie, New York
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1450
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1451
    - Third floor plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1452
    - Front elevation, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1453
    - Rear elevation, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1454
    - Side elevation, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1455
    - Side elevation, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1456
    - Section, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1457
    - Miscellaneous details, Undated (Folder 44a)
      Sheet # 1458
    - Miscellaneous details, Undated (Folder 44a)
      Sheet # 1459
  - Franklin, H. H. Location: Syracuse, New York
    - Studies for sunroom adjacent to diving room, 1907 (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1695
    - Detail of fountain in sun room, 1907 (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1795
      Scale: 1 1/8"=1'; Full
      Note:IMPORTANT: The Sheets are numbered up to 1758 in sequence and then start from 1795 onwards. There are no Sheets with numbers 1759-1794
    - Plan of terraces, 1907 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1826
    - Garden wall details, 1907 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1827
    - Detail of wood fence and gates, 1907 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1828
      Scale: 3"=1'
    - Plan of terraces, 1907 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1829
  - George N. Pierce Company Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Study for a garden, 1904 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 494
      Format: Brown Line
    - Study for a garden, 1904 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 495
      Format: Ink on Mylar
    - Lot plan, showing location of buildings, by Architect S. H. Woodruff, Undated (Box 20)
      Sheet # 496
    - Planting plan, 1905 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 497
    - Details for coping and step, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 498
    - Rough study for garden plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 499
    - Rough planting plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 500
    - Details for coping and step, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 501
    - Planting plan, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 502
    - Plan for a garden, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 503
    - Details for coping and step, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 504
    - Planting plan, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 505
    - Grading plan, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 506
    - Lot plan, showing location of buildings, by Architect S. H. Woodruff, Undated (Box 20)
      Sheet # 507
    - Planting plan, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 508
    - Grading plan, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 509
    - Study for paving pattern in Garden, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 510
  - Gilbert, Fitch Location: Gilbertsville, New York
    - Perspective sketch of terrace and terrace house, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 350
    - Topographic map of Gilbert Cemetery lots, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 351
      Format: Heavy Construction Paper
    - Details of gates between garden and farmyard, 1913 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 382
    - Sketch of balustrade, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 383
    - Front elevation, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 384
    - 3/4" scale details of Dipping well, 1913 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 385
    - Scale detail of Bird house post, 1913 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 386
      Scale: 2"=1'
    - 1/4" scale elevations of garden walls, 1913 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 387
    - Scale details of Garden house, 1913 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 388
    - Gate from garden to work yard, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 389
      Scale: Full and 3/4"=1'
    - 3/4" scale details of garden house and arbor, 1913 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 390
    - Plan and elevation of farm gate and stile, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 391
    - Gate leading from garden to stable yard, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 392
    - Garden house and pergola screening stables, 1913 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 393
    - Plan of the new terrace and summer house, 1914 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 394
    - Foundation plans of the new terrace and summerhouse, 1914 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 395
    - Plan of roof of summerhouse and pergola, 1914 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 396
    - Elevation towards porch - new terrace and summerhouse, 1914 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 397
    - Elevation looking toward billiard room - new terrace and summerhouse, 1914 (Box 17)
      Sheet # 398
    - Garden borders at meadow brook, 1914 (Box 18)
      Sheet # 399
      Scale: 1"=5'
    - Rough sketch of pergola, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 400
    - Rough sketch of pergola, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 401
    - Studies for window treatment, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 402
    - Rough plan and elevation of pergola, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 403
    - Rough plan and elevation of pergola, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 404
    - Perspective sketch of pergola, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 405
    - Detailed perspective sketch of pergola, Undated (Folder 21)
      Sheet # 406
    - Measurement for laying out drive, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 407
      Format: Note paper
    - Detail of opening into pergola, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 408
      Scale: Full and 1/4"=1'
    - Partial plan of garden arrangement, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 409
    - Rough plan of pergola, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 410
    - Paving plan for pergola area, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 411
    - Garden borders at meadow park, Undated (Folder 21)
      Sheet # 412
    - General plan of site arrangement, 1913 (Folder 21)
      Sheet # 413
    - Garden house and pergola screening stables, 1913 (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1515
    - Description unspecified, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1516
  - Grant Location: Unspecified
    - Topo, Undated (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1325
    - Line A, Topo, Undated (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1326
    - Line B, Topo, Undated (Box 46)
    - Topo, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1327
    - Road Profiles, 1912 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1328
  - Greening, Edward Location: Monroe, Michigan
    - Party room details, Undated (Folder 9)
      Sheet # 89
    - Sketch of Ceiling plan / Party room, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 90
    - Elevation and Plan of Party room, Undated (Box 6)
      Sheet # 91
    - Sketch of House plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 92
    - Sketch of Floor plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 93
    - Sketch of Floor plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 94
    - Sketch of Exterior Elevation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 95
    - Preliminary sketch of Site plan, Undated (Folder 9)
      Sheet # 96
    - Interior elevations of Party room, 1923 (Box 6)
      Sheet # 97
    - Plan and details of Party room, 1923 (Box 6)
      Sheet # 98
      Scale: 1/2"=1' and full scale
  - Hawley, H. B. Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Second floor, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1836
    - Side elevation, likely, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1837
    - Front elevation, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1838
    - First floor, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1839
    - Various details, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1840
    - Interior details, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1841
    - Elevation towards porch, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1842
    - Elevation from terrace, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1843
    - Floor plan of residence, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1844
  - Hay, Mrs. John Location: Wade Park allotment, Cleveland, Ohio (or unspecified)
    - Plan for arrangement and planting, 1909 (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1682
      Format: Linen - blue
    - Main entrance drive, Undated (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1872
  - Hees, J. Ledlie Location: Sacandaga Park, NY, (or unspecified)
    - Gate and stone posts, 1912 (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1863
    - Front elevation, Undated (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1866
    - First floor plan - alteration, Undated (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1868
    - Elevation showing veranda treatment, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1912
    - Sketch "Old scheme", Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1913
    - Lattice to be covered with vines (gate post), Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1914
    - Sketch "First scheme", Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1915
    - Brick gate post, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1916
    - Rough sketch of decoration for gate post, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1917
    - Elevation, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1918
    - Description unspecified, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1919
    - Porch, likely, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1920
    - Rough sketch, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1921
    - Sketch and figures - new entrance, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1922
      Format: Stationery
    - Suggestion #1 (layout of tennis and croquet courts, etc.), Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1923
    - Suggestion #2 (Courts), Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1924
    - Suggestion #3 (Courts), Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1925
    - Rough sketches, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1926
    - Rough sketches, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1927
    - Rough sketches, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1928
    - Sketches of gate post, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1929
    - Culvert, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1930
    - Tennis court - Re-established grades, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1931
    - Sketch for stair arrangement, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1932
    - Rough drawing, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1933
    - Sketch of proposed location of servant's lodge, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1934
    - Proposed fence for stable yard, 1906 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1935
    - Bird fountain details, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1936
    - Re-established grades of tennis court, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1937
    - Rough landscaping sketch, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1938
    - Proposed fence for stable yard, 1906 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1939
    - Bridge, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1940
    - Lattice work, likely, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1941
    - Proposed fence for stable yard, 1906 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1942
      Note:Architect, Augustus D. Shepard, Jr.
    - Children's house, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1943
    - Children's house, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1944
    - Children's house, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1945
    - Children's house, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1946
    - Children's house, 1911 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1947
    - Survey, 1905 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1948
    - Bird fountain details, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Sheet # 1949
    - Pergola, Undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1959
    - Playhouse garden, Undated (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1960
    - Gates to the property, 1912 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1961
    - Full scale detail of lamp, 1913 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1962
    - Study for alterations, Undated (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1963
    - Study for alterations, Undated (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1964
      Scale: 1"=8'
    - Tennis court, 1912 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1965
    - Plans for arrangement about house site, 1905 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1966
    - Tennis court, 1912 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1967
    - Plan for changes, 1912 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1968
    - Survey of property about house site, 1905 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1969
    - Study for alterations, Undated (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1970
    - Sketches of pergola, house etc (Composite), Undated (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1971
    - Gate and stone posts, 1912 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1972
    - Full scale detail Copper lamp, 1912 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1973
    - Top of the post at the entrance, Undated (Folder 52)
      Sheet # 1975
    - Wrought iron work of gates, 1912 (Folder 52)
      Sheet # 1976
  - Henning, J.C. Location: Louisville, Kentucky
    - Plan of arrangement, 1913 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1805
  - Hert, A. T. Location: Louisville, Kentucky
    - Garden plan, 1911 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 111
  - Hewitt, Mr. & Mrs. Leonard Location: Louisville, Kentucky
    - Sketch plan of arrangement, Undated (Folder 24)
      Sheet # 662
    - Portion of topographical survey of "The Beeches", 1915 (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1681
    - Plan of garden, Undated (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1684
    - Details of pergola, Undated (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1685
    - Details of pergola "C-C" and "D-D", Undated (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1686
    - Typical detail of pergolas and terminals, Undated (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1687
    - Miscellaneous details for garden, Undated (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1688
    - Detail of garden wall, Undated (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1689
    - Detail of garden/house, Undated (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1690
  - Hoffman, Alma Location: Grosse Pointe, Michigan
    - Elevation sketches, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 944
    - Elevation sketches, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 945
    - Elevation sketch, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 946
    - Elevation sketch, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 947
    - Elevation sketch, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 948
    - Elevation sketch, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 949
    - Elevation sketch, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 950
    - Elevation sketch, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 951
    - Elevation sketch, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 952
    - Elevation sketch, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 953
    - Elevation sketch, 1924 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 954
    - Site plan sketch, 1924 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 955
    - Site plan sketch, 1924 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 956
      Scale: 1"=60'
    - Site plan sketch, 1924 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 957
    - Diagram of existing trees, 1924 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 958
    - Preliminary site plan, 1924 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 959
      Scale: 1"=16'
    - Preliminary site plan, 1924 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 960
- Series II. Clients J-P
  - Junior League Home for Crippled Children Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - Sketch of wing wall at Service court, 1929 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1421
    - Sketch for motor entrance, 1929 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1422
    - General plan, 1929 (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1429
  - Jurden, Ralph L. Location: Memphis, Tennessee
    - Elevations of Living room, 1924 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 754
    - Details of Columns, Gutters, Undated (Box 30)
      Sheet # 755
    - Paneling details, Undated (Box 30)
      Sheet # 756
    - Sketch of east elevation of Living room, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 757
    - First floor plan, Scheme "A", 1924 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 758
    - Partial first floor plan, Undated (Box 30)
      Sheet # 759
    - Second floor plan, Scheme "C", Undated (Box 30)
      Sheet # 760
    - First floor plan, Scheme "B", Undated (Box 30)
      Sheet # 761
    - Second floor plan, Scheme "C", Undated (Box 30)
      Sheet # 762
    - Second floor plan, Scheme "A", 1924 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 763
    - Revised second floor plan, 1924 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 764
    - Front Elevation, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 765
      Note:By Architect Charles O. Pfeil - Set of drawings for previous owner, Dr. E. C. Ellett
    - Right side elevation, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 766
      Note:By Architect Charles O. Pfeil
    - Left side elevation, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 767
    - Rear elevation, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 768
    - Rear elevation, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 769
    - Plan of second floor, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 770
    - Plan of foundation, 1914 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 771
    - Plan of second floor, 1914 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 772
    - Plan of first floor, 1914 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 773
    - Left side elevation, 1914 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 774
    - Right side elevation, 1914 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 775
    - Plan of roof, 1914 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 776
    - Front elevation, 1914 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 777
    - Plan of foundation, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 778
    - Plan of first floor, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 779
    - Plan of roof, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 780
    - Garage plan, 1913 (Box 30)
      Sheet # 781
    - Sketch of east elevation of Living room, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 782
  - Location: Kansas City, Missouri
    - Perspective sketch, Shelter and Pool Treatment, 1925 (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1415
    - General landscape scene, 1929 (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1416
  - Kidd, J. Howard Location: Penfield, New York
    - Basement and foundation plan, 1937 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 720
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 29)
      Sheet # 721
    - First floor plan, 1937 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 722
    - Basement and foundation plan, Undated (Box 29)
      Sheet # 723
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 29)
      Sheet # 724
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 29)
      Sheet # 725
    - Third floor plan, Undated (Box 29)
      Sheet # 726
    - Heating plan, 1937 (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1801
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1802
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1803
      Condition:Good to Fair
    - Attic floor plan, Undated (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1804
  - Kinney, O. A. Location: Cortland, New York
    - Planting plan, 1909 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 470
    - Planting plan, 1909 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 475
    - Plan for arrangement of property, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 476
      Format: Ink and watercolor on Mylar
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 477
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 478
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 479
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 480
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 481
    - Plan for arrangement of property, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 482
    - Plan for arrangement of property, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 483
    - Plan for arrangement of property, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 484
    - Plan for arrangement of property, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 485
    - Plan for arrangement of property, 1907 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 486
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 487
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 488
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 489
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 490
    - Plan for arrangement of property, 1907 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 491
    - Details of wood and stone, 1907 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 492
    - Grading measurements, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 523
      Format: Construction paper, likely
    - West and South elevations of residence, by architect Wm. H. Miller, 1906 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 531
  - Knox, C. B. Location: Johnstown, New York (or unspecified)
    - Door and window trim, Second story, Undated (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1359
    - Interior details, Undated (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1360
    - Masonry work for Greenhouses, 1905 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1361
    - Greenhouse plans, 1905 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1362
    - Greenhouse plans, Undated (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1363
    - Conservatory plans, 1910 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1364
    - Greenhouse plans, Undated (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1365
    - Detail of Hanger to carry seat, Undated (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1366
  - Lea, Luke Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - 1925 (Folder 42b)
      Sheet # 1403
  - Lockhart, James H. Location: Coraopolis Heights, Pennsylvania
    - Perspective of Stable Group, 1916 (Box 33)
      Sheet # 848
      Format: Pencil and Crayon on tracing paper
    - Sketch of Gardener's cottage, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1162
  - Lyon, J. Dennison Location: Sewickley Heights, Pennsylvania
    - Detail of garden house, 1916 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1431
    - Working plan for revision of garden, 1915 (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1432
    - Detail of pool coping, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1433
    - Alterations and additions to main terrace, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1434
    - Details of garden steps and piers, 1916 (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1436
    - Garden wall copings, 1916 (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1437
    - Alterations to garden walls, Undated (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1438
    - Details, Garden wall copings (5 sheets), 1916 (Folder 43a)
      Sheet # 1439
  - Massey, Mrs. W. E. H. Location: Denton Park farm, Toronto, Ontario
    - A road system for residence and garden, Undated (Folder 30)
      Sheet # 752
    - Plan of west porch, stone borders and steps, 1916 (Folder 30)
      Sheet # 753
  - Massey, Jr. Location: Unspecified
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1167
      Format: Tracing Paper
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1168
    - Sketch plan outline, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1169
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1170
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1171
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1172
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1173
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1174
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1175
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1176
    - Rough elevation sketch, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1177
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1178
    - Rough sketch plan and perspective, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1179
    - Rough sketch plans, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1180
    - North west entrance façade, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1181
      Format: Pencil and Colored pencil on tracing paper
    - Garden façade - elevation, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1182
    - Perspective sketch of house, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1183
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1184
    - Rough roof plan, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1185
      Format: Colored pencil on tracing paper
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1186
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1187
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1188
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1189
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1190
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1191
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1192
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1193
    - Sketch plan of House and Terrace, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1194
    - Sketch plan of House and Terrace, Undated (Folder 39)
      Sheet # 1195
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1196
    - Rough sketch plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1197